# Egirin Gega

Senior Web Software Developer

## Profile

HTML and CSS. Also have knowledge and experience in different Web Development frameworks and tools such as Symfony, Nodejs, Angular, Sand others.

I have successfully designed, developed and supported live-user applications (tvomathify.com & www.gsb.co.tz). I have good communication skills with the clients gained on my experience while developing web sites for local businesses in Albania.

#### **Details**

Mandalletrale 21 Graz 2010



# Employment History

# Web Developer at ALB Development, Tirana

December 2014 — February 2016

Developer and Programmer for different types of WebPages.

Using platforms like:

- Wordpress
- Joomla

## Full-Stack Web Developer at DM Consulting, Tirana

March 2016 — April 2017

I was responsible for the development of websites for local businesses.

I performed a lot of DevOps duties as well!

#### Front-End Web Developer at Kesson Group Albania, Tirana

April 2017 — March 2019

At this company my duties were, developing and maintaining different components for the website:

#### www.teachaway.com

I have also worked on another project as a Front-End Developer, which has this website:

https://www.skooli.com/

Worked as Lead Developer on:

https://tvomathify.com

### Front-End Web Developer at Idobet, Tirana

April 2019 — October 2019

I have been key part of the development team that provided Sport Betting Platforms for mobile and online in Third World Countries such as Uganda, Tanzania, Kenia etc.

The Platforms are build using Angular for the Online Sites & Javascript for the mobile Site.

## Skills

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

SQL

PHP

Adobe Photoshop

Agile and Scrum

**DevOps** 

API

# Languages

English

German

Italian

#### **Hobbies**

Cycling, Football, Racing ...

## Front-End Web Developer at Pessl Instruments, Graz

November 2019 - May 2020

During my time at this company i worked Part-time Front-End Developer for their software service called IMeteos.

The platform was made in angular and i was responsible for updating a couple of components.

# Education

## Bachelor in Computer Engineering, Epoka University, Tirana

October 2011 — October 2014

Preffered subjects:

Electrical & Electronic Circuits, Database Management Systems, Digital Design, Data Structures, Computer Networks, Artificial Intelligence

I Fundamentals of System Administration, Operating Systems, Introduction to Distributed Systems.

## Master in Computer Science, Technische Universität Graz, Graz

October 2019 — Present

# Internships

## IT Specialist at ALBTelekom, Tirana

June 2013 — September 2013

I was responsible for the well functioning of all systems that were assigned to me by the IT manager.

# Y Extra-curricular activities

#### Student Assistant at Epoka University, Tirana

October 2012 — June 2013

Student Assistant, C&C++ Programming.

# ■ References

References available upon request